Arun BS

Software Engineer III

Personal Info

Address:

26/b, 13th Cross Road, Pragathi Layout,

Doddanekundi

Bangalore - 560037

Phone:

9739185574

E-mail:

bsarunmca@gmail.com

Date of birth:

1989-10-30

Portfolio:

https://bsarunmca.github.io/Portfolio/

Skills

React JS, Redux

JavaScript, ES6

jQuery

NodeJS

Webpack

Python

Angular JS (1.x)

AJAX, JSON

HTML, HTML5

CSS, CSS3, SCSS

Bootstrap

Lesshint, JSInspect

Achievements

Toshiba:

~ Worked at Japan for technical collaboration and establishing communication bridge between teams

~ Award wining project in a Tech fare at Toshiba : WebPanel Style Guide. This project is a toolkit for developing the MFP UI.

Payoda:

 \sim SPOT award for New tool exploration and helping the team

~ SPOT award for fixing critical issue

Creative front end developer with 7+ years of work experience in developing the web application and embedded application as per W3 Standards. Onsite experience(Japan) to discuss about the architecture and planning for the upcoming projects of MFP and supporting MSM and TSIP. Team player with good listening skills and innovative ideas to make attractive designs and development. Good exposure to AGILE and SCRUM methodologies.

Experience

2019-12 - **Software Engineer III**

present NCR Corporation

Money Moment

Tech stack: ReactJS, Redux, GCP, Webpack, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JSON, MUI,

GIT, etc...

Description: NCR Digital Banking is a provider of online banking software to banks and

banking application on Payee, Payment, Template and Report module etc...

credit unions. My role and responsibility is to lead a team and develop UI for 'US'

2017-11 - Senior Software Engineer

2019-12 Toshiba Software India Private Limted

WebPanel

Tech stack: ReactJS, Redux, ESLint, Python, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, JavaScript

 $\textbf{Description}: To shiba\ Printer\ has\ embedded\ browser\ for\ MFP\ (Multi\ Functional$

printers). My role is to develop UI for MFP. Traveled Japan(Onsite) to discuss about the architecture and planning for the upcoming modules and establish communication bridge

between Toshiba MSM and Toshiba TSIP.

2015-12 - **Software Engineer**

2017-11 Payoda Technologies

Arista CVP

Tech stack: HTML5, CSS3, Angularjs, jQuery, d3js, Requirejs, AJAX, JSON, NPM,

Grunt, ESLint, Lesshint, JSInspect, Jasmine.

Description: CLOUDVISION is a central portal for managing all the network switches making it easier to configure and monitor better than ever. CVP combines a front-end web-based dashboard for performing the pre-integrated operational workflows and a

backend state repository and analytics engine for maintaining historic network state.

2014-07 - Frontend Developer

2015-11 Sakhatech Information Systems Pvt. Ltd

TNT, Tellofy

Tech stack: CSS3, Bootstrap 3.0, JQuery, AJAX, JSON, Facebook API, Google plus

API, Twiter API, & Linkedin API

Description: Web applications for shipping company.

TNT – Customer, TNT - Customer Care, TNT – PUD(Purchase and delivery details)

Education

2010 - Erode Arts and Science College

2013 • MCA - Master of Computer Application

2006 - **Jairam Arts & Science College**

• BSc - Maths with Computer Application